Contact

markonimobile@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ zoranzokimarkovic (LinkedIn) zmarkoni.github.io/ (Portfolio) github.com/zmarkoni (Other)

Top Skills

Front-end Development React.js ES6

Languages

Serbian (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Accelerated JavaScript Training
Website Performance Optimization
Testing Clientside JavaScript
EF SET English Certificate B2
UPPER INTERMEDIATE
JavaScript Testing with Jasmine

Zoran Markovic

Senior Frontend Developer at Netcentric, A Cognizant Digital Business

Berlin, Berlin, Germany

Summary

Senior Front-end developer with focus on React.js

Experienced Magento / WordPress / Bootstrap / AEM Front-End developer.

As a professional developer with strong background featuring a master degree in Computer Science I am completely committed for quality, with passion to explore new tools (like Angular, React) and to upgrade 'old' ones, like Webpack, Gulp, Bootstrap...

Experience

Netcentric, A Cognizant Digital Business 3 years 8 months

Senior Frontend Developer October 2019 - Present (5 months) Berlin Area, Germany

Front End developer July 2016 - October 2019 (3 years 4 months) Berlin, Germany

AEM, REACT

Codeplicity doo Front End Developer March 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 4 months) Novi Sad

As a senior at Codeplicity, I worked on a custom platform which is capable of running thousands of applications from a single engine. Good planning and organizing the code is essence in order to support multiple projects from the same platform. I worked in a front-end team where we love to write nice, readable and reusable code.

LTF International
Front-end developer
September 2012 - January 2015 (2 years 5 months)
Novi Sad, Serbia

LTF International is a digital agency with headquarters in Sydney. It's focus is on developing custom websites and e-commerce stores based on Magento, Neto and Ebay platforms. As front end developer my job was to translate design in functional website, and creating custom tools to satisfy the clients need.

Innovagency
Front-end developer
January 2012 - August 2012 (8 months)
14C RUA CASTILHO, 1250-069 Lisbon, Portugal.

Right after I graduated, i have joined the AIESEC and went to Lisbon on technical practice. In Innovagency I have gained my first working experience and opportunity to work in multinational team.

Education

Faculty of Electronic Engineering and Computer Science Master of Computer Applications (M.C.A.), Computer Programming · (2005 - 2011)